# **Geraldine Ragsac**

Front-End Designer & Developer

# Summary

Creative, detail-oriented designer & developer. Five years of experience as a designer generalist with an affinity for code. Love education, personal development, and UX design. I'm here to empower small entities who lack an online presence and technological expertise, to bring people closer to better versions of themselves.

# **Work Experience**

## **Graphic Designer & Web Developer | Mar 2019 - Present**

Shepherd Research Lab | Honolulu, HI

### Shepherd Research Lab Multisite on WordPress Webmaster

- Designed and launched six websites in WordPress to give the lab an online presence, attracting new collaborations and customers
- Managed website and social media content, including social media posts, Facebook Ads, and emails via Mailchimp

<u>Breast Density Workshops Event Planner & Coordinator</u> www.BreastDensityWorkshop.org

- Converted a live conference to a 1-day virtual conference with 6 hours of talks, poster session, and vendor hall for 200 attendees
- Managed a team of 3 other event planners to ensure deliverables were on time
- Created art assets for the virtual space using Adobe Photoshop in pixel art style, adding a fun game-like atmosphere to the experience
- Led efforts in copywriting, web design, and web management for conference websites

### **DXA Scan Analyst**

- Trained and validated to analyze various DXA scans
- Programmed scripts in AutoHotKey to automate systematic review and printing of reports, saving time and effort

#### Digital Artist | Jan 2018 - Oct 2018

The Girl Who Sees | Remote

- Painted in-game art assets using Adobe Photoshop to match the game's existing art style
- Led the design for and designed battle scene screens and UI for various scenarios

### Science Teacher | Jun 2015 - Jun 2017

James Campbell High School | Ewa Beach, HI

- Developed and taught year-long curriculum for three courses: 9th grade Physical Science, 12th grade Physics, 12th grade IB Biology HL, managing three classes of 20-30 students daily
- Organized and maintained accurate records of attendance, classwork and homework, and grades for 70-80 students per year

#### Contact

Email: hello@geraldiner.com

Portfolio: <a href="https://geraldiner.com">https://geraldiner.com</a>

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/geraldiner

GitHub: <a href="mailto:github.com/geraldiner">github.com/geraldiner</a>

#### Skills

**Design:** UX Design, UI Design, User Research, Storyboarding, User Flows, Sketching, Ideation, Wireframes, Prototyping, Visual Design

**Design Tools:** Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, Experience

Design - XD)

**Technologies:** Git, Visual Studio Code, WordPress, Google App Script (JavaScript)

Code: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Markdown, Python, AutoHotKey

# Education

B.S. Human Centered Design & Engineering

University of Washington - Seattle, WA